Everyone was warned,
but nobody paid attention.
The temperature was rising...
the oceanic patterns changed...
and the polar ice melted.
They called it extreme weather.
Nobody knew what "extreme" was.
In the year 2019...
hurricanes...
tornadoes...
floods...
and droughts...
They unleashed a wave of
destruction on our planet.
We not only lost towns...
or beaches.
We lost entire cities.
The East River swallowed Lower Manhattan.
The heat claimed 2 million
lives in Madrid...
in just one day.
But at that moment...
to face extinction...
It was clear that the inauguration
could solve this problem alone.
The world joined in the fight...
and we fought.
Scientists from 17 countries...
led by USA and China...
They worked tirelessly.
Not as representatives of their nations...
but of humanity.
They found a way to
neutralize the storms...
with a network of thousands of satellites...
that launch countermeasures to control
the basic elements of climate...
the heat, the pressure and the water.
All supervised by the
International Space Station.
They gave a technical name
to the satellite network...
but we all call him
Little Hero of Holland...
by the legend of the child who covered
the drain of a dam with his finger.
This is what saved us all.
And it was built by a
team led by a man...
Geo - Storm
my father.
- Thank you.
- Keep the change.
Jake Lawson. I have one...
Senate hearing in room 12.
Yes.
Lawson?
- The Little Hero of Holland, right?
- Yes
Old man, I have to shake his hand.
Agree.
Twister?
Goodbye!
Blizzard?
Monsoon?
- Goodbye?
- Goodbye!
Everyone here is in debt
to you, Jake Lawson.
If you need something, just ask.
The Senate Commission that
oversees the Little Dutch Hero...
you will hear Jacob Lawson...
Head of Climatology
Operations of the ISS.
Let it be recorded in minutes that
he arrived almost an hour late.
Yes, sorry for the delay.
Literally, I came flying
from outer space.
We started.
Mr. Lawson, we are
at a crossroads.
As you know, according to
UN Resolution 28-14...
The United States will cede control
of the Little Hero of Holland...
to an International Supervisory
Commission within 3 years.
This is despite the fact
that we build everything.
Excuse me, Senator.
I do not want to delay things.
Did you say "we" build everything?
Yes it is.
Because I know what I did. I led
the team that built the station.
I was accompanied by an international
team of 600 people, not just Americans.
And I know everyone's face,
but I do not remember theirs.
We had a plumber there.
He had a slight resemblance to you.
Very smart, Mr. Lawson.
Yes, the Little Hero of the Netherlands was
an international effort and, yes, someday...
Max Basta
It could be of the world.
But until then, we have
authority over its operation.
And we have authority over you!
And you have been making
fun of that authority.
I have one report after another here.
Non-compliance with procedures...
several infractions of
the chain of command.
And then, there was an incident where
he hit a federal inspector in the face.
Your federal inspector does not know...
that a capacitor has charge
even if it is disconnected.
I was going to grab him with my hands.
I saved his life!
You can put all the excuses
you want, Mr. Lawson...
but there is something
that he can not defend.
The day he connected the
Little Hero of Holland!
Max BASTA
and activated it without our consent!
And what would that have caused, Senator?
There were storms brewing in Southeast
Asia and the North Atlantic...
that would have killed dozens
of thousands of people.
The Little Hero of Holland was ready.
We activate it. Works. You're welcome.
Mr. Lawson, if you continue
to challenge our authority...
Max Coopera. Please.
... the Little Hero of Holland
will continue without you!
Is it clear to you?
Yes.
All right. And one more thing.
To ensure compliance, the commission
will send more support staff.
Logically, when they assume, they will
have to fire part of their staff.
We will leave this decision to you.
Senator, with all due respect,
my team did nothing wrong.
Excuse me,
I have not asked for your opinion.
These people left their home and their
family and risked their lives...
to save the planet.
The session is over.
I'm not going to fire anybody!
Sorry?
People like you need people like me.
For what?
To be able to accredit the merit
of everything we achieved.
To be able to go with their
constituents and cronies...
The session is over.
And her lovers, to show off...
- and say. "Look at me!"
- Sit down!
- I'm watching, Senator.
- Sorry.
- We watch everyone.
- The session is over.
The session is over! Thank you.
Was it going well enough, what was not?
Until a certain point.
No, Jake, it never went well.
But why are you good, little brother?
To smooth edges, calm the waters?
You can fix it. As usual.
It's like a talent.
It is a talent.
Something like that.
If only I could help you. Really.
But it's not that simple...
not this time.
Why not?
Since last week, I was put in charge
of the Little Hero of Holland.
It's great!
It's great! Are you kidding?
Tell me you're kidding.
Listen, what do you want me to do?
You do not leave me an option.
I told you that this should go well, but no.
I'm sorry, Jake.
You are fired.
THREE YEARS LATER
DESERT OF RECISTAN, AFGHANISTAN
God. It's more than 50
degrees in this thing.
UN
Dispérsense.
Hi, Agent Wilson.
Under Secretary Lawson.
It looks good today.
I have the same as always.
Not quite.
Have you seen that I have a new tie?
I watched him. We are trained to
notice any disturbing detail.
- Sarah, please.
- Assistant Secretary Lawson...
I'm not allowed to engage in casual
conversations while I'm working.
They watch us.
They always watch us.
If so,
what is the point of hiding something?
It interferes with my tasks.
I would prefer not to shoot him.
It would be an honor to be
the first person you kill.
Just a moment.
What's going on?
The President convened
a security meeting.
It was not programmed, so
now I guess I'm in service.
I like the tie.
At home at 7:00. I love you.
Sorry, I did not hear you.
I said nothing.
Circle, sir.
Yes ma'am.
What the hell happened here?
One of our thermospheric satellites
failed over Afghanistan.
He was found by a UN
recognition team.
And is the Climate Council aware?
Yes, and they agreed to maintain discretion.
But many know it, I do not know
how long the secret lasts.
And do we know that it was
because of the Little Hero?
No doubt.
Can we assume that it is an
isolated incident? Doctor Quigley?
We are pretty sure, yes.
It is good to know that
they are "quite safe".
It is a serious failure.
What is your proposal?
Simple. Cancel all satellites
in Central Asia...
until you know what happened.
- Are you serious?
- Yes
Do you know what it cost
to connect all nations?
We try hard...
to assure these nations that the system
will protect them and it has been that way.
And let's not forget
that it's election year.
If we cancel it, the
press will come to us.
OMG!
300 people died in that village.
Who the hell cares about politics?
We are responsible for their deaths.
The only thing that should
worry us is how to solve it...
and make sure it does not happen again.
And how do you propose that we do that?
We can not do anything.
The problem will not be
solved from this place...
nor will we.
We do not need an international
team at the station.
Not executives.
Engineers, programmers, technicians...
to make a comprehensive
review of the systems...
no matter the cost or the policy...
and we need them there now.
We will transfer all the authority
of the Little Hero of Holland...
to an international
community in two weeks.
I will not be the president who
delivers damaged products.
Not now, not never.
We will handle this problem and
its solution internally...
and we will send a man.
One of ours, that reports only
to us and that we can control.
It is understood?
Look for that person.
Now.
Yes sir.
I know you will not like it, but...
There is only one person for this.
Your brother, Jake.
Come on, Jake no.
Seventeen countries...
They had teams working on that.
Everyone reported to him.
No one knows better than
him what is behind him.
Come on. Can we
consider other options?
Max, how long have you known me?
Since I entered the Department of State.
So is. I selected you.
I believed in you. You're smart.
And I was not wrong with you.
Not with Jake either.
If it sees to be a problem...
No sir.
All right.
Afghan satellite zero nine six entering.
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION IV
MAINTENANCE OF THE SMALL HERO
All teams prepare for the
incoming Afghan satellite.
Standby replacement satellite.
Afghan satellite secured.
Authorized replacement for the launch.
The 5-A satellite has taken off.
Decompression chamber
doors closed.
I want a complete analysis
of all the components.
Priority one.
Beginning Afghan satellite analysis.
I will take care of this.
That depressurize the fuel intake.
I understand.
COMPLETE TRANSFER
Makmound. Hey, Makmound!
I'm about to surpass your record, man.
I have to reprogram something.
Come on!
That guy does not value what he has.
Please, clear the doors.
Uncle Max?
Hello! What are you doing there?
What is that? A solar generator?
Solar access cable generator with
tracking. Replaces the transformer.
God!
Every day you look more like your father.
Where did you find it?
Are you really asking that?
Of course.
He built it, right? Come here.
I'm glad to see you!
How are you? All right?
Great.
What's going on here?
I can not believe it.
You should be nine years old.
Thirteen.
You should be part of my life...
but they are things that happen.
Auch.
How is everything here?
Do you live with him now?
I come two weekends a month.
All right. How is your mom?
Angry, and rightly so.
I imagine.
Hannah, everything ready.
How are you, Jake?
Hannah, I told you not
to talk to strangers.
Come on. Ignore him.
When your dad and I were your age...
We were so close that
we had a secret code.
- It is true.
- Seriously?
I do not remember.
Of course.
Do not.
Well, it was nice to see you.
Listen, take care of yourself.
What are all these parts of cars?
I build electric motors for
the retirees of Vero Beach.
It keeps me busy
You are for more than this.
Are you kidding?
I'm having a better time than ever.
It's a bit early, do not you think?
I was fired by my own brother.
Then I lost my family...
my house, my dog...
happy hour starts at 11:00 here.
You saw your niece, you do not want beer.
The exit is there.
There are problems with the
Little Hero of Holland.
No, it's not like that.
A whole village of some
dead may disagree with you.
Yes.
And then yesterday, a
compartment opened alone.
We lost one of our team.
The Little Hero is no longer my problem.
That's stupid.
Because in addition to your daughter
and your beloved soccer club...
the Little Hero was all
that mattered to you.
If before.
Yes, but you took over.
Do not care?
Do not?
So, what are you doing living here?
Hey, I know you consider me a rat...
someone who moves chess
pieces to make a living.
Guess what, yes. It is true.
But that's how you get 17 countries
to agree to build a space station.
You build things, do not you?
And there is something
wrong with what you built...
and people are dying.
If you really believe you are the
best I know that it is like this...
How the hell can you
stand there and say no?
I'll have to take orders
from someone, I suppose.
Yes.
So what? Is it a yes?
As long as it's not from you, yes.
CIC - COUNCIL OF THE PACIFIC
CLIMATE HONG KONG, CHINA
NAME CHENG LONG PASSWORD
HEAD OF ENGINEERING, PACIFIC
DIVISION ACCESS GRANTED
AFGHANISTAN DISPLAYS
"SUCCESSFUL"
Hi, I'm Max. Leave a message.
There is no place for you, a cat.
Do you have room for me there?
EXTERIOR TEMPERATURE 57 DEGREES C.
- 135 DEGREES F
All right.
I think that's all.
I prepared a lunch for you too.
Did you hear about the gas
explosions in Hong Kong?
Yes, I just saw it on the news.
It's awful.
Is it similar to what
happened in Afghanistan?
No, nothing happened in Afghanistan.
Are you going to fly into space?
- Do not.
- Yes, you will!
You will go today to fix the Little Hero.
What did I tell you to hear
other people's conversations?
You never told me anything about that.
You do not do much as a father.
How do you know it is safe?
Of course it is safe.
I've been there hundreds of times.
Do not treat me like a girl.
Someone died!
- It was an accident.
- He sucked space.
It was an accident.
That's what I'm going to fix, okay?
You do not have to worry
Do what I go on vacation
for a week or two.
To a place at 400 k towards nothing?
With temperature of -270 degree?
Go vacation.
If you're right.
Why did Uncle Max fire you?
Amazing!
You did something wrong?
No, listen, your uncle Max and I...
It's not just about work.
Sometimes, younger siblings
hate being minors.
And they start giving orders.
They think they know everything.
They tell you how to act, how to talk...
and after decades, you
just get tired of that.
Maybe you should listen to him.
They came looking for me.
- I have to go.
- What?
I thought I would take
you to the airport.
Do you really want to see mom? Great!
We can fly home together in Atlanta.
I already took care of everything.
Stop making yourself angry.
Hannah, what do you want from me?
I want you to come back alive.
And you are not exactly
the most reliable type.
Hears.
I know I have not always
kept my promises...
but I will return.
- I...
- Promise it.
I promise.
Come here.
I'll be back soon, will I?
CAPE CAÑAVERAL, FLORIDA
KENNEDY SPACE CENTER
OV-104 is one hour from takeoff
and ready for boarding.
We are a minute away
and in the countdown.
Good trip sir.
Separation of the
propellant rocket confirmed.
I hate to interrupt, Major Tom...
But in a few seconds, you should
be able to see the network.
How does it feel to be back home?
Look at you, baby.
Alive and kicking.
Mr. Lawson.
Hi.
Ute Fassbinder.
Haunted.
Yes, I remember you.
If you were the demented scientist.
You were here when I was.
Thermosphere, right?
Yes.
The communication
cover needs sealer...
where the APT conduits pass through
the carcass of the channel.
Not well. That's wrong.
And did you hear that?
- I am sorry.
- Listen out.
That buzz?
It is a damaged reducer transformer.
You have to take care of all those things.
- Mr. Lawson.
- I do not know. It's not your fault...
but when I left,
everything was perfect.
Maybe I should talk to your Chief Scientist
about the fine art of crap in everything.
I am not the Chief Scientist.
I was promoted a year ago.
Fine Congratulations.
One of our team died this week, Mr.
Lawson.
I'm sorry about the transformer.
Let me introduce you to your team.
Of course, an American.
Actually my brother and I were born
in the United Kingdom, but thank you.
Yes, but he has the
American flag on his arm...
and the look pillars.
No offense. The situation is serious...
and we do not want to be controlled
by a puppet from Washington.
Is not that so, comrades?
Well, I'm already here.
So let's start with
the names and posts.
Adisa, structural engineering.
Duncan Taylor, analyst systems
and loyal British citizen.
Hernández, robotics.
Dussette
Satellite communications and security.
And you?
He is Mr. Jake Lawson.
Are you Jake Lawson?
The famous Jake Lawson?
He looks much older than he thought.
I mean, it looks good...
but his physical appearance does not...
It does not match the lapse
that has happened in your life.
I am going to be fired?
Well, we do not have much time.
We must examine three situations.
Afghanistan, the scientist who died here,
the and the new incident in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
No, that was a gas explosion.
We all saw it on television.
All right. Keep believing that.
I, on the other hand...
I have a mystery that I would like
to solve to avoid more deaths...
so add whatever you want.
Luck!
Fast question.
Active sniper...
the President and I are
in the line of fire.
Who do you save first? To me...
To the president.
Come on. You could have
thought about it a second.
Sorry honey.
Work is first, as you do.
No it's not true.
No, I have priorities, and you...
you are my priority.
Come on, let's do it.
I want to do it...
but you keep talking.
Why do we always have to hide?
Come on, let's do it. Let's get married.
We can not.
It goes against the rules.
One day, honey.
You are going to answer the phone.
Because your work is first.
Do not...
I'm going to attend because I do not
want it to interfere with this.
You see?
Now maybe I will not save you.
Yes, hello?
Max, I'm Cheng.
Cheng, God, tell me
you're in Hong Kong.
- Cheng?
- Last night...
I was right in the middle of everything.
It was horrible. That's why I call.
They just reset the phones.
Yes, you're lucky to be alive.
- Those gas pipes?
- I'm not sure it was that.
What do you mean? I do not understand.
It was hellish heat
before they exploded.
The satellite sensor should
have registered it, right?
I checked a thousand times, but I can
not get to the Hong Kong satellite.
They blocked my access.
ACCESS DENIED
Check your "HoloFrame".
I do not understand. We both have access.
EEI IV STARTING SESSION
Exact.
DENIED ACCESS
And the only ones with the authority
to block it are there with you.
Wait. What do you mean?
If someone covers a system defect...
There could be a critical
failure worldwide.
If the Little Hero
has a big fault...
can create something much worse
than what we try to avoid...
bone, a geotormenta.
What? Slow down, Cheng, yes?
One that?
A geotormenta.
Climatic catastrophes occurring
simultaneously with the whole world.
By exceeding a minimum threshold,
storms will cause new storms...
as a chain reaction,
until merged together.
It has to be a technical fault.
I'll call you when I know something.
Agree. Thank you.
These pipes have not been
maintained for years.
Gas pipelines would cause
explosions in Hong Kong.
Cheng believes that Hong Kong
is related to the Little Hero.
It is suggesting a
kind of cover-up.
I received a message, and the
President called a meeting.
What, can not you stay?
When the duty calls, there is no option.
"Neither the rain, nor the snow, nor
the darkness of the night," right?
Honey, that's the Postal Service.
We are the Secret Service.
Is there any difference? Really?
I did not know, I did not know it.
Check everything.
Find out what he knows.
Take your laptop. Come on.
The satellite that failed in
Afghanistan, what kind was it?
It is my favorite. I call him "rocanrolero".
The SR-22.
Use sonic probes to slow down molecular
movements and generate cold...
but in that case, it froze everything.
Why?
We do not know.
We reviewed the hard drives...
but the fault eliminated the records.
All right. Let's review all
the "Rocanroleros" we have...
to see if we find any
corruption in their records.
Show me all the "rocanroleros"
In the net.
There must be more than a thousand.
1,270, to be exact.
And we are going to review them one by one.
Dana Hi.
Hi. What are you doing here?
What do I do here?
I work here. I'm your boss.
Yes, but why did you
get off Mount Olympus?
To see me in the Village of the Millennials?
I have to ask you a favor.
You are the best at what you do.
But I need this
to be between us.
All right.
I have a problem with my HoloFrame.
Do I look like Technical Support?
I am sorry. I'm sitting here
defending the free world...
against cyberterrorists...
But Grandpa needs
to fix his phone.
No, but I have problems accessing
the G-22 satellite in Hong Kong.
A satellite without communication.
Often happens.
No, not a satellite.
Everybody.
Oh
I'm somewhat intrigued. Stay.
CONNECTING WITH THE CLIENT...
All right.
It seems a common
interruption of the line...
bad server relay
or trunk failure.
Are you still with the Secret Service girl?
What? Do not.
No, I'm not dating anyone
Wait see. OMG.
Someone wanted to block your access
without you knowing it was intentional.
But this...
This is very intentional,
and very intelligent.
And I know what you're going to say.
You will say: "Do not tell anyone."
And I will not do it.
But I did not get
ready to sit all day.
So whatever happens, I
want to take action.
Hopefully there is no action.
What if...
do not tell anyone.
Miss Fassbinder, a request for priority
communication has just arrived.
From Climatology Center?
Of the White House.
With which all of DC we
have to deal with this?
I think I would become
the boss of the fools.
Hello boys.
Max told me you do not have a
good opinion of politicians
I did not say that.
Me neither.
It was very difficult for the
world to join this program.
We have come too far to fail.
You and I understand that
we can not allow it.
Yes sir.
If I discover something, I
will inform you immediately.
Actually, you will report everything to Max.
Good luck.
Begin
Thank my Lord.
I will leave you alone.
And if you need me, I'll be in my office.
Thank you.
Do I have to inform you all?
You lied to me.
Again.
No, I just did not agree to
your ridiculous request.
How do I turn this off?
There is something you should know.
We are having problems here to
access the Little Hero signal.
We have reason to believe that...
It may not have been accidental.
Is not it accidental?
I tried to access the
Hong Kong satellite.
I knew it!
You think it's possible?
If possible.
But even if you accessed the
Hong Kong satellite remotely...
you would not get the
records you need.
No. That information must be extracted
from here, from the same satellite.
All right. I can authorize it.
I do not need your
authorization for anything.
I'm sure this terrifies you...
but what if you just trust that I
will do my job and you thank me?
I trust you.
Do you remember the first
time I took you out of jail?
God, good heavens!
Yes, it was a week after
the death of mom and dad.
They arrested you for fighting you.
There I realized that despite
everything I was living...
I would have to take care of you.
Okay, do you know why?
All right. It is what it is.
I guess I did not have
another to trust you.
But if you ever authorize
something without my approval...
you will go straight home.
End of stream.
Hong Kong Satellite 022
entering to be examined.
Very good.
Disarm this and we'll see
what happened in Hong Kong.
Lower it
I should have gone down already.
What is that?
I have no idea.
- Well, deactivate it.
- It does not respond.
Heavens, Hernandez!
Get out of here! already!
Let someone open this door, now!
Watch out!
Fuck!
Let's pick up every piece of this thing...
and let's take it to production.
Can we recover the records
of the hard drives?
The accident caused a short
circuit and burned all the discs.
Look. It is destroyed.
So did we lose all
possibly corrupt discs?
Not all.
What do you mean?
I was analyzing your video of the
accident that killed Makmound.
Each of the honeycombs that
flew has a disk inside.
And one of them was embedded
in the communications tower.
It seems that the stamps are still intact.
If we are lucky, the corrupt
disk will remain inside.
We have to recover that panel.
Yes, hello?
I just got to DC. We must see each other
I've solved everything.
See you at 10:00 in front of the
square where we used to have lunch.
In college.
Agree. Yes, I will be there.
Ready for decompression.
Very good. The door is open, guys.
You can leave now.
Cross the threshold of
gravity and follow me.
Let's recover the panel and
see what's on those discs.
All right.
There is the panel.
Wait. Just a moment.
We designed the tower to be able to
withdraw the equipment in an emergency...
so the bars are easy to move.
Control, the panel is insured.
It is understood.
Now come back, guys. Come back
We are coming back.
Jake, what's wrong?
I do not know!
Jake? Jake!
I can not control the damn suit!
- What happens?
- Your suit is failing.
- Jake, do you copy?
- Duncan, tell him to cut it.
Jake, cut the fuel intake.
It does not respond!
Resist, Jake.
I can not hold it.
Eject the bulge!
Heavens. We're going to lose it.
You're good?
Yes.
Do you have the disc?
I took it when I released the panel.
You destroyed a dozen communication
links, TCAS sensors...
I am fine, thank you very much.
What happened out there?
The impeller was locked.
And you lost the door panel,
so there are no disc codes.
To start from scratch.
Great.
Why did not you tell them about the record?
Because someone tried to kill me.
I know my team. I trust them.
You think you know them.
But someone does not want us
to see what's on this record.
Jake, there's corruption here at all.
The doors did not fly accidentally.
They were programmed like this.
- It was not a failure.
- Do not.
Someone killed Makmoud deliberately.
No doubt the same person who
manipulated the Hong Kong satellite.
The access records were deleted.
We do not have fingerprints.
No. That's what they believe.
The access records are synchronized
with the central server.
Yes, but that is the problem.
If they are deleted in the
place, they are deleted in all.
No, in all those who know.
When we built the Little Hero,
we included a secure library.
Something that will track
and archive everything.
The information on our
saboteur will be there.
COMPLETE REVISION "NO CURRUPTO"
ENXIO - NO device or address
Do not.
The service rejected the key
They blocked you
But who?
The virtual conference room.
How many have access to
these transmissions?
Anyone with access level three or more.
Dozens of people
Max.
- Max.
- What?
Just relax. It will arrive.
What, really? Do I look nervous?
A bit.
There is.
I arrive?
Do not!
Cheng! OMG!
This is Agent Wilson.
Yes, I need an ambulance right now.
- Duppont Circle Street
- Max...
Agent Wilson, I sent the ambulance.
I'm here.
I'm here. Look at me.
Zeus.
What?
Starting virtual conference.
Max? You're good?
They said it is urgent. What's going on?
Yes.
I wanted to apologize.
Apologize?
If you had any idea
what happened to me...
Did you make me come
here just to apologize?
All right. Agree.
Apology accepted.
Hey, Max, we do not
turn our backs on you.
It is the tactical code between brothers.
Do you remember that day
that dad took us fishing?
Yes,
he dropped his cell phone at Key Biscayne.
Prove that we are not fishermen.
Four hours...
none of the three caught anything.
Then he poured the sabotage
to Dad's reel to leave.
The pin on the top,
I pulled hard...
up to the top level.
The spool mechanism was activated.
Dad, spy of the government has
always caught me in infraganti.
And I do not take long to say "I want to ask
you to trust". It is never pleasant to fail.
"But I do not prefer not
to fish with my family...
before fishing 20 fish alone. "
I did not even understand
what he meant at that moment.
But now yes.
Take care, Max.
End of stream.
What was that?
It was the first decent
conversation we had in years.
- Hears.
- OMG!
Can you calm down?
What?
Do you have a moment?
Yes! I received your message.
God.
Did Barbie leave you
from the Secret Service?
I need to show you something.
Watch this.
Do you remember that day
that dad took us fishing?
He dropped his cell phone at Key Biscayne.
Dad never took us fishing.
How sad.
I am sorry.
I'm not good with
family problems...
and the friendship.
What? Do not.
It is a code.
"He dropped his cell phone at Key Biscayne."
Your mobile number is the key.
Look at the digits.
The first number is the first word.
The second number, nine,
advances nine words.
That is the second word.
Third number, nine again.
Another nine, you advance.
Then nine, two, nine, five...
and so on until you get a
totally different message.
Who came up with this
coding, a 12-year-old boy?
No. I was 13 when I did it.
All right.
Then, one-nine-nine-nine...
two-nine-five-five...
eight-seven-one and let's go.
Sabotage test in upper
part of the government.
Never trust
You said you wanted action.
Yes, but... fuck it.
If you do not want to continue with this,
I understand.
No. If I want, I just...
I want and I do not want to.
It's like climbing a roller
coaster or eating in "Chipotle".
What is our next step?
Well, I need you to find something
in a file called "Project Zeus."
"Project Zeus"?
Yes.
It seems like a conspiracy
theory between brothers.
Just execute the damn search.
I get a result.
With double encryption.
A compulsive obsessive.
Can you decrypt it?
Yes, I could...
but not from here.
It's a protected network of the
White House, and you can not hack.
I do not have credentials to access.
Fuck. Me neither.
I do not know anyone who has.
Of course.
Max?
Stop there.
Fuck!
High! Honey, relax!
Who is this girl in our house?
I can explain everything.
It sounds very perverted.
- Shut up.
- Sorry I will.
I broke one of your wine glasses.
He fell, I'll pay you.
I have the money. I am sorry.
Speaks.
She is Dana, she works with
me in the State Department.
I asked him to come
because I need help...
and it turns out that
now, I also need help.
It's sexy!
I know how much your work means to you.
I took an oath, Max.
We have rules.
If that's why, do not live together either.
Dana
You ask me to commit a crime.
You ask a Secret Service agent to
enter the White House server...
and obtain files illegally.
And you thought I would say yes!
- I still think you'll say yes.
- Why?
Because I'm asking you.
And if I ask you...
well, it must be important.
And you know it's more
important than me and you.
"You and I".
Shut up.
Sarah, please.
Once.
We must watch the security
videos without alerting anyone.
Someone killed Makmound.
If we discover why, we
know who is behind.
But you can not access the
cameras without entering.
We go to the security server room.
You see? In the end it was
useful that he built it.
Yes, but I live here.
Pedantic.
Makmound was diagnosing
the Afghan satellite...
while we were launching a replacement.
Motherfucker.
He took something out of the satellite.
The poor bastard realized...
and they killed him so
that nobody else knew.
No cameras are allowed
in the changing rooms.
Then let's go see him in person.
Which is the code?
Seven, six, three, six, three.
What do you think they do?
You know what happened to
me was not an accident.
Whoever did that...
he killed Makmount.
And what makes you think that it's not me?
Because if it were you,
I would already be dead.
Dussette, lower the weapon.
Whatever they are looking for...
It is not in this wardrobe.
I was here when Makmound came in.
He put his things in an empty locker.
Why did not you tell me?
You watched the same security video as me.
I was waiting to see who was
coming for the Makmound things.
Is here.
Two, six, six, five, three.
Bingo.
This is all he copied from the
satellite to his HoloFrame.
It's a virus.
It was not generated by the
computer on board the satellite.
Because they implanted it.
Markmound discovered the virus and
murdered him before he told it.
I get it. OK, here we go.
Zeus Project.
There are tens of thousands
of storm simulations here...
the starting place changes.
LEVEL OF GEOTORMENTA
SEQUENCE OF SIMULATION
They all end in the same way.
A geotormenta.
We never saw something like that.
Dana, show us just the simulation
that starts in Afghanistan.
Yeah right.
START PLACE Registan, Afghanistan
Possible scenarios:
Now filter that...
so that the second fault
is about Hong Kong.
Where are you going with this?
What if Cheng realized that someone
was following one of his scenarios?
Making it look like a predicted
pattern of failure...
disguising a crime as a
series of accidents.
They could be accidents.
If so, they would not have killed him.
Someone has turned the
Little Hero into a weapon.
GEOTROMENTA SEQUENCE
Starting virtual conference.
Hi.
A new face?
If a friend.
It will keep us out of the channels...
so we're fine
- Did you get my message?
- I received it.
It's worse than we think.
They are using the Little
Hero to attack cities.
Yes, they are passing their
movements through failures.
They already killed the
man who discovered this...
and I do not think they're over.
Yes.
It was my life's work, Max.
They said it was impossible...
but we did it.
And it worked...
perfectly, without failures, day
after day, year after year.
And what do people do with that?
It makes it a weapon.
I know.
I know. It's not too late.
We can solve it.
Before it is repeated,
but I can not alone.
I need you.
Tell me how they control the Little Hero.
- I know others control it.
- How?
A virus.
Can you stop it?
There is only one way.
We can temporarily turn
off the Little Hero.
When you start it, the system is cleaned...
the virus is eliminated, and the
operating system is protected.
All right. Let's do it
I authorize it.
Yes, I think it's clear that I
do not wait for your permission.
It is not a Chromebook.
Do not turn it off with a button.
You need the codes.
And the only one who has
them is the President.
Let's go and let's say what we know.
No. You can not go to see Palma.
We need more evidence than I have.
We're talking about putting
out the Little Hero.
Even for an hour, it
puts the planet at risk.
No, I think you do not understand.
Someone blocked alternative
system access.
An access that almost nobody knew existed.
But the President does.
No, Jake, come on. What?
Are you crazy?
I'm not saying it's al.
It is only a possibility.
Who else has the
resources to do this?
Homicide, cover-up, a virus that can
only be stopped with codes that he has.
Why? Tell me why.
Why do that?
We are two weeks away from transferring
the Little Hero to the rest of the world.
Two weeks of losing
autonomous control.
Your speech is good, but it
will never allow it to happen.
A series of disasters, in an
international team to blame...
and you must cancel the transfer.
And who would blame him?
Very good. Do not set aside
the view of your satellites.
Max.
Max, do not do any stupidity.
Come on.
They already tried to kill me once.
Max!
End of stream!
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
President Palma. a couple of questions.
Any comments before going to the
national convention in Orlando?
Any statement?
A moment before going to Orlando?
My friends from Washington, DC...
they could not get on a plane without
first greeting them. It is impossible.
What are you doing here?
- Are you crazy?
- Sarah, listen.
Jake needs us to steal
the codes from Palma.
US?
You ask me to help you for your brother...
with which you have not
spoken for three years.
Yes.
Think about it. Afghanistan, Hong Kong,
Cheng, the shit of simulation...
the death of the space station.
Come on.
You have to trust me, yes?
I'm not kidding.
- All right.
- Look.
The codes are in the
HoloFrame of Palma.
It can not be done on the plane.
Why not?
Too many eyes He is never alone.
Well, then what do we do?
Palma wants time alone to shower and
make calls before the holidays.
Follow him I'll let you in.
I can steal the codes while bathing.
- That's the idea.
- Yes
- Warning.
- Move.
Satellite communications without connection.
Team, report yourself at the stations.
OMG.
We have about 200 satellites
that report failures...
most are critical.
Get satellite information
with more critical overload.
TOKYO CRITICAL ALERT
We lost all control over
the Tokyo satellite.
TOKYO, JAPAN
Max.
I did not know you were
coming to the convention.
Yes. My dad comes from Florida...
so I promised that I would take it.
We need all the votes, right?
Yes, bring him to the rest room.
We will make some photos.
He is very kind, sir. Thank you.
We report extreme weather anomalies...
in Brazil, Mexico, Bucharest and Belgrade.
There are more than a thousand
storm alerts around the world.
RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL
Satellite of Rio de Janeiro, critical.
Recovery routine without connection.
Let's change course!
Approach us to the nearest
critical satellites.
What are you trying to do?
We will launch the replacements. As
many as we can, as quickly as possible.
We must recover the
other satellites first.
Or replacements will hit them.
They are programmed to arrive...
exactly the same destination.
And they will knock out
the infected satellites.
- Yes
- Of course!
Report to the stations...
for replacement of the Rio satellite.
Authorized launch
Replacement of Rio satellite on the way.
Warning. Satellite
on collision path.
Deactivates the retro propellers.
That does not slow down.
J93 DISCONNECTED
Load them and keep coming!
Warning. Geotormenta alert.
GEOTORMENTA ALERT
TIME FOR GEOTORMY
Time for the geotormenta: 1:30 minutes.
ORLANDO FLORIDA NATIONAL
DEMOCRATIC CONVENTION
Four more years!
Thank you. As you know the environment...
It was the great passion of my late wife.
And I know I would be very proud...
caused by the worst
hail in history.
There was an extreme climate event
this time in Rio de Janeiro.
A cold front of the coast
rapidly advanced...
with marked decrease in
temperature in the city.
Several deaths are reported...
Tokyo and Rio de Janeiro
affected by extreme weather
But the number is still unknown.
A cargo plane...
It could have crashed in the city,
probably because of the extreme cold.
Tokyo and Rio are the first catastrophes
since the launch of the Little Hero.
POSSIBLE SCENARIOS "1".
We'll be back after the break
with our reporter Sally Jones.
NEXT LOCATION Orlando,
Florida, USA.
TIME FOR GEOTORMY
God.
Hey, Max!
Where is your dad?
Know what? I was very anxious.
I recruited you for this position myself.
I know everything about you.
Your brother, and the
death of your mother...
the death of your father, everything.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you insist on making this trip?
Tell me what happens.
Maybe I can help you, maybe not.
Okay, look.
I must tell you something. Come here.
In 90 minutes there will be a global
storm from which we will not recover.
And I need the President's codes.
As you say?
We must turn off the Little Hero, now.
Are you serious.
He said he hired me because
he believed in me, right?
Well, I need you to believe me now.
We must inform the President.
Go to Cape Canaveral.
No. We can not do that, sir.
Why not?
I think he's the one who started this.
Together we'll stay.
United, we can.
Four more years!
You better be very sure to
make accusations like that.
With all due respect, we do
not have time to discuss.
I know Palma.
Why do that? It's crazy
Yes, well, he is doing it.
Do you have evidence?
Yes, I have evidence. Dozens of files.
In the Zeus Project. It's all there.
We can not get the
President's codes.
Why not?
Because he is the code.
Biometric data Ten fingerprints,
two retina scans.
Well what do we do?
I'll have to make him come to his senses.
We will both have to do it.
Satellite is critical in Florida.
Load the replacement, now.
Station self-destruction
sequence initiated.
SELF-DESTRUCTION OF STATION IN
PROGRESS - BEGINNING OF PHASE ONE
Phase one starting now.
All right. Deactivate that!
I can not. I blocked.
We incorporate manual controls.
Yes, I try.
DENIED ACCESS SELF-DESTRUCTION
IN PROGRESS
Without station, we will
not control the satellites
OPERATING SATELLITE STATUS
Self destruction?
Why did you put self-destruction?
In case it fell on Earth.
Where is Duncan?
He is the only one who knows
how to cancel the commands.
Duncan.
The fuel tanks.
They are the first to be destroyed.
Then the sections to the
command and recovery.
Well, everyone to the ships!
Evacuate!
Come on, we must hurry! Go!
Jake What are you doing here yet?
That felt good.
I've wanted to do it since I met you.
You've gone mad?
Yes, enough
The virus.
Only you could have
put it in the system.
Only you could have blocked
the alternative access.
Only you could have done this.
I need the manual controls
for self-destruction, now!
For what?
I will not be here when it explodes.
But you do.
Come on man. Because you did?
Do you know how much they
pay us poor scientists?
Multiply that by a thousand.
What difference will it make?
If you do not stop, there will be
no planet to spend all of that.
Please.
Let's keep the best places.
Do not you get curious
about flying to the world?
No. Because millions of
people are going to die.
And one of them is my daughter.
Fuck.
MOXLEY STADIUM
Room for the President on the left.
We will face it there.
Zeus Project.
Did Cheng tell you something else?
Cheng?
But this president knows
that hope is not a plan.
This president knows...
that despite how far we got...
There is a lot of work to be done.
Work to save our planet...
It's my priority as vice president.
VIDEPRESIDENTE MILLER
This is a step towards success...
and the greatness that can be and
will be the future of our society.
Excuse me.
That's why I'm with the
House spokesman tonight...
the provisional president of the senate,
and the whole cabinet of President Palma.
We are all united to support...
Palma does not leave the building.
- Yes sir.
- Come on.
Where were you?
Come here.
It's not the President, is it? It's Dekkom.
Dekkom? How do you know?
Because he just tried to kill me.
That's why I know.
According to the simulation,
Orlando is the next affected city.
Here? Why do that?
Because he wants Palma
to be trapped here.
And all the others who are still
in line for the presidency.
Are we going to steal the codes anyway?
The code is the same President, yes?
They are biometric codes.
If Palma dies, the Little
Hero can not be stopped.
Sure, kidnaps the President.
Sounds reasonable.
Yes, well, that's all we have left.
Unless you want to steal
her fingers and eyes.
Let's move on.
Get a car
I will seek the President.
Okay, fine.
The program did not get the immense
international support that...
Handler located. President committed.
Evacuate to Alfa safe area.
Get him out of here!
Come on.
Secret Service! Come back!
Location of the shooters?
Mezzanine, exit 212!
Two men with automatic!
- I go. Find the President!
- You...
protect the entrance! Let no one pass!
Let no one pass!
Anechoic chamber, Lammy.
- It is understood!
- You two...
... clear the emergency exit!
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
You have to come with me.
This exit is not allowed!
Please, keep calm.
Really? An autonomous taxi?
Dana stole it from afar.
It's the only thing I got.
What's going on here, Lawson?
Please sir.
I'll explain everything in the car.
Please sir!
We do not have much time!
Move! Get on the ships!
Keep moving!
Quick!
Time for the geotormenta: 55 minutes.
Sir, I barely hear it.
The storm is causing a lot of static.
The Secret Service will follow the
signal of the President's HoloFrame.
They must reach him before them.
Under no circumstances
can you leave Orlando.
Our man at the space
station did his job.
- Now you have yours.
- It is understood.
- Dekkom?
- It's the perfect weapon, sir.
Dekkom tries to change the world map.
And that? Blame a fault?
Yes, to that and to a dead president.
He will assume the position after killing
everyone in the line of succession.
NATIONAL DEMOCRATIC CONVENTION
MILLER VICE PRESIDENT
Holy God.
- Let's cover! Under the bridge.
- Mr.
MOSCOW RUSSIA
You are implicating the
State Service in this.
Do you realize that you are committing...?
Treason, Yes. I kidnapped the President.
I stole state secrets.
Something I forgot, honey?
Sweetie?
Guilty.
It took Dekkon years to plan this, sir.
The president's agenda always changes.
Today is the day and date
that I knew would not move.
Getting my brother and I to lead
the investigation was a trap.
Think about it.
He hired us to fail.
Get down!
Well,
he says he's going to clear up again...
between four and 91.
I have to take care of a
little problem first.
Hold on!
Do not!
Marry her
No. We're fine here.
A thunderstorm in Orlando caused
a terrible explosion in the CND.
There is no official information on
the whereabouts of the President...
I do not know.
I can not communicate with Jake.
And they inform us that there are
explosions in the space station.
Honey, Orlando's storm is
approaching your dad's house.
I can not locate it He wrote you?
It's not there.
It's there.
Of a serious problem
in the space station.
Attention to all teams.
They are boarding the last ship.
Approach the assigned ship immediately.
Ship launch sequence initiated.
Jake
- I'm not going.
- What?
When my brother gets the codes...
I must execute the program.
No. We must go.
We have not heard from him in hours.
I trust him.
You know that the restart
must be done manually.
Then I stay.
I am the commander.
Do not.
I'm the only one my brother
will entrust with the codes...
I need your HoloFrame.
You must manually insert
it into the server kernel.
You can find it, right?
- Yes
- All right.
Goodbye, Ute.
Auf Widersehen, Jake.
Station there.
The President's signal indicates
that he is coming to us.
Do you really want to go back there?
Yes, as soon as I pass, I
will be the only survivor...
ready to assume as the next
President of the United States.
Here they come.
Shoot.
Did you think the President was
the only one who could be traced?
- How...?
- How?
Because I'm the damn President
of the United States of America.
You're finished, Leonard.
It's all yours.
Wait! Wait a minute.
I have given you an opportunity,
Mr. President
I should take advantage of it.
An opportunity? Release it!
It's genocide, Leonard!
You say genocide, I say
preemptive strike.
You've gone mad!
The sun will come out tomorrow.
Our enemies will have disappeared.
Eliminated as by divine grace.
Why would you do this?
Because nobody else would.
I'm going back to the year 1945...
when the USA It was a bright city,
not a bank disguised as a country.
Playing to be God?
What the hell is the little
Hero if it's not playing God?
Ask Max. He knows.
Science is about playing at being God.
Sometimes God does
not play very clean.
Yes, well,
do you know what my brother would say?
What?
Get him out of here!
Come on, Lawson!
That is my fiancé.
DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES
CAPE CAÑAVERAL, FLORIDA
KENNEDY SPACE CENTER
Take the President to guard! Quick!
TIME FOR GEOTORMENTA
Mr. President
We have the codes.
You must hurry.
The station is in full closing.
And the team?
Safe.
But Jake decided to stay.
To restart the satellites.
Your brother is waiting for you.
Come on.
Starting virtual conference.
Hi.
Jake
Jake, it was Dekkom.
I said I could be wrong.
Mr. President
How is Hannah?
All right. You are safe.
Atlanta was not affected.
Thank God.
Valid identification Initiating
closure protocol transfer.
It will take 60 seconds to load.
How much for self-destruction?
Eight minutes...
more or less.
Mr. Lawson...
we appreciate your delivery.
Wait. What the hell is going on?
You've done your part, Max.
Jake, what's wrong?
Now it's time to do mine.
Do not.
The codes do not stop
self-destruction, right?
Do not?
Do not...
only the geotormenta.
The self-destruction of the
station can not be reversed.
Come on. There must be a form.
Come on. It's all my fault.
I'm the one who put you there!
Hey, it's fine.
I wanted to go. It was my decision.
God knows...
I did not always make
the right decisions.
You were right, little brother.
I had to take care of you.
But you took care of me.
Can you forgive me?
Yes always.
Take care of my daughter.
Be part of your life.
I will do it.
We should have done this
a long time ago, right?
Yes.
You're a good man, Jake.
See you, boy.
Complete transfer
COMPLETE TRANSFER
Time for the geotormenta:
5 minutes, 51 seconds.
Warning. The core
rotation has finished.
We do not know what happens there.
We only know that the station has suffered
some kind of devastating accident.
They tell us that there
is no fix or salvation.
Sweetie.
Will come back.
He promised me.
We will keep you informed
with the latest developments.
TIME FOR GEOTORMY
Self-destruction entering phase four.
Invalid code
DELETED
Need help?
Wrong door.
What are you doing here?
I told you. I live here.
Time for the geotormenta:
1 minute, 40 seconds.
INTERFACE DETECTED
Loading codes.
Satellite closure in progress.
When the last satellite completes
the cycle, let me know.
I will restart the whole system manually.
- That should eliminate the virus.
- All right.
ON
Five seconds.
Three.
- C'mon darling.
- Two.
And one.
Restarting manual activated.
GEOTORMENTA WARNING
Status: Restarting.
The network was restored.
The virus is not there
RESET OF THE SYSTEM IN PROCESS
Transferring control to NASA.
CONTROL OF SATELLITE NETWORK
TRANSFER IN PROGRESS
COMPLETE TRANSFER
Jake!
I have you!
Warning. Self-destruction
entering the final phase.
The best view of all.
Ute...
Do you believe in miracles?
Follow me We must reach the satellite.
I have you.
We must get as far away as possible
before the final detonation.
Decoupling.
COMPLETE SELF-DESTRUCTION
And apparently, we've
lost the space station.
A tragic end for the two
heroes still on board.
Hey, Max, look at this.
I detect emergency lights...
They are issuing distress signals.
See if one of the ships can return.
With luck, someone will see it.
Cross your fingers.
Hernandez, son of a bitch!
Thank the Mexican.
Yes! Come here. Yes!
SHIP ATERIZES A SAVE
A true miracle.
The ship they see brings all
the members of the ISS home...
who stayed at the station.
Hi, Kake. I'm Sarah, Max's fiancee.
Welcome to the family.
Well done, both.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Mr. President
Yeah, well, you made a mistake again, Jake.
How many times should I tell you?
Never listen to me
God, I'm happy to have you back.
It's good to be back.
SIX MONTHS LATER
Nice place you have here, Jake.
Thank you.
When do you go back there?
- In a week.
- Yes?
Yes, much remains to be done.
But I will return.
I know.
- This sucks.
- Yes, seriously, it's very boring.
Do you know what?
I can not stand a second more.
Why did you make us do this?
I do not know. I tried to relive the moment.
The moment? What a moment?
We never went fishing with dad.
Invent all that history.
Yes, but it was great, right?
You must admit it.
He had moral in everything.
Moral? What moral?
You can not reverse the past.
You can only face what is to come.
NASA maintained the satellites while
we rebuilt the space station.
We made it safer, stronger.
It belongs to all of us now.
A planet, a single people.
As long as we remember that we
share a future, we will survive.